manuallinkbuilding.co.uk 2013-09-28

# Privacy Policy - Link Building Services | SEO Outsourcing | Link Building Company | SEO Link Building

**Our Principles**  
We (Gareth Hoyle Ltd t/a Manual [Link Building](http://uk.manuallinkbuilding.com/link-building/ "Link Building")) respect your personal information. We recognise that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. That’s why we have put a policy in place to protect your personal information. This policy describes what we do with that information.  
**What Information Do We Collect?**  
(Gareth Hoyle Ltd t/a Manual [Link Building](http://uk.manuallinkbuilding.com/link-building/ "Link Building")) is the sole owner of the information collected on Manual [Link Building](http://uk.manuallinkbuilding.com/link-building/ "Link Building")’s Website.  
We collect aggregate statistics about all customers, traffic patterns and related site information, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.  
You are not obliged to give us any personal information in order to use our website.  
We collect some basic details from those who make a specific request for brochures, newsletters or other general enquiries. This includes your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and postcode. We may also ask some further, voluntary questions so we can gain a clearer understanding of our users exact requirements and preferences.  
After fulfilling any specific request we will not Contact you again (unless you have given us permission to do so) with any other information, although your details will be retained on our records for statistical purposes only.  
**“COOKIES”**  
“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive.  
Our cookies enable us to provide you with more personal service, but they never contain personally identifiable information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that if you would rather not store the information for future use.  
**How Do We Protect Customer Information**  
UK Data Protection Legislation means we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information that you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access.  
• We ensure that any personal information we keep is as accurate as possible. This may include using third parties to check and improve name and address data.  
• Under the Data Protection Act you may request details of personal information we hold about you. Please send such requests to Gareth Hoyle Ltd, 1st Floor Builder House, Mayors Road, Altrincham, Cheshire. WA15 9RP. United Kingdom marked for the attention of “Gareth Hoyle Ltd – Compliance Department”. An official fee will be payable. If you believe that any information we hold about you is incorrect or incomplete, you should write without delay to the Compliance Department at the same address. Any information, which is found to be incorrect, will be corrected promptly.  
Will Gareth Hoyle Ltd Disclose the Information it Collects to Outside Parties?  
Gareth Hoyle Ltd will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others unless you have given us your permission. With your permission we will only share the information with carefully chosen, reputable and trustworthy third parties.  
We may provide aggregate statistics about customers, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.  
**Removal from Mailing Lists**  
You can always remove your name and Contact details from our various email-lists and other lists. To do this, please contact Gareth Hoyle Ltd’s Compliance Department. If you want to be removed from a Gareth Hoyle Ltd mailing list, please write to Gareth Hoyle Ltd, 1st Floor Builder House, Mayors Road, Altrincham, Cheshire. WA15 9RP  
**Communications from the Site**  
• Special Offers and Updates  
At several points throughout the site, you may be presented with an option to receive occasional information on products, services, and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we operate an ‘opt-in’ mailing list subscription policy, so we won’t sign you up for anything without your express permission.  
• Unsubscribe Facility  
All e-mails from Gareth Hoyle Ltd will include an “unsubscribe” option allowing the recipient the opportunity to advise us that they no longer wish to receive any further messages from Gareth Hoyle Ltd.  
**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.  
**Improvements**  
Gareth Hoyle Ltd is committed to improving the service and information we are able to provide our users. We are therefore continually seeking ways of improving and upgrading this website. With this in mind, we reserve the right to change the way this site operates and how we process information. However, we will continue to respect the privacy and preferences of all users of this website.
